As the days grow dim
A shadow with nowhere to belong hangs uneasy
It looks pathetic as though it's begging for forgiveness
What I sowed begins to take root
You're starting to grow cold
I reach out only to slip right through
Will things ever go back to how they were?
I'm swallowed by the surging waves of blue
Destroying my future as I move
Will the end ever come?
Even if I'm broken
Even if I'm torn
Even if I fall apart in disgrace
I'm not afraid of anything anymore
Because I've long since been empty
Grant me this wish
Please put out this flame for me when it's all over
I don't want anything anymore
Because I'm afraid of losing again
It's almost dawn but the fog still hasn't lifted
While the path ahead remains unclear
I follow it forward