>Typesetting
--not Stage but Title yes
--Exiled
2.        Gojo Satoru has been deemed an accomplice in the Shibuya Incident
and is hereby exiled from the jujutsu world.
Any attempt to free him from his seal will be considered a crime.
2.        Gojo Satoru has been deemed an accomplice in the Shibuya Incident
and is hereby exiled from the jujutsu world.
Any attempt to free him from his seal will be considered a crime.
2.        Gojo Satoru has been deemed an accomplice in the Shibuya Incident
and is hereby exiled from the jujutsu world.
Any attempt to free him from his seal will be considered a crime.
2.        Gojo Satoru has been deemed an accomplice in the Shibuya Incident
and is hereby exiled from the jujutsu world.
Any attempt to free him from his seal will be considered a crime.
2.        Gojo Satoru has been deemed an accomplice in the Shibuya Incident
and is hereby exiled from the jujutsu world.
Any attempt to free him from his seal will be considered a crime.
2.        Gojo Satoru has been deemed an accomplice in the Shibuya Incident
and is hereby exiled from the jujutsu world.
Any attempt to free him from his seal will be considered a crime.
2.        Gojo Satoru has been deemed an accomplice in the Shibuya Incident
and is hereby exiled from the jujutsu world.
Any attempt to free him from his seal will be considered a crime.
2.        Gojo Satoru has been deemed an accomplice in the Shibuya Incident
and is hereby exiled from the jujutsu world.
Any attempt to free him from his seal will be considered a crime.
2.        Gojo Satoru has been deemed an accomplice in the Shibuya Incident
and is hereby exiled from the jujutsu world.
Any attempt to free him from his seal will be considered a crime.
2.        Gojo Satoru has been deemed an accomplice in the Shibuya Incident
and is hereby exiled from the jujutsu world.
Any attempt to free him from his seal will be considered a crime.
--Bottom text
Kumiya Juzo's Masterpiece
Cursed Tool: Dragon Bone
Secret Art: Falling Blossom Emotion
Cursed Technique: Blazing Courage
--Ep Title
Episode 51
Perfect Preparation
Kukuru Unit Captain: Zenin Nobuaki
Are you listening?
--Are you listening?
Hei
Head of the Hei: Zenin Naoya
--Report
q
h
u
LAJUSSOm'i
.UXwO"O49D
.n4:yJ"oK;
EODxtoZ"?B
1.adxOqSCF
UbTUin2HOs
29X3PIzhad
QcoMXPESYO
kRdM8;XX8A
Q1zhk4E"'!
JRchZzn3xz
DPSZluU1hj
pAwH7;,XFV
2FrIVj"LyN
bIA7WgJG9Y
jK5ekUF"nS
BbPzsShP1A
AofJqmbGy9
YV,'L9VVfN
MctYQRgZI:
8sB3e5fZr8
oVvd6?Uar0
Fn9P;;ouAh
.;ESR1bk:8
sT6;TXmPBe
z0elLOXv'E
hB,MO?g5j7
h,Yo!y8Nhu
EEVIWC:NKq
,zAGTkp,rx
yTri5'Wa:E
RiVrm?LYyn
i:aqs4d',A
Hkq.r7"tma
7h2MXE:t50
U4mcuJHwC4
9v6R2TB;x;
ZubWUQgFWJ
umXcKT7SaW
U2jXJQqFRl
tjzAQG667F
1O?GqpQPFj
YTPrG?kdYP
'RXVBJsBn5
GwS4vDv65C
VQ8IvKMSJa
V,anxoYH!E
!T!Bs0J3w0
CYNHcp54bG
RcV9iOa'yE
!!MopXgt,y
zod'izDWV:
2HUv."Jg3Y
tnk0oeUFyv
3qDs5.X42!
lKaftk1cOw
40wkz!,GoC
I'7AdAZPf8
FsIV1VGvDX
gRQQ0020CE
Jrb2AQqpm8
pfhbLFd?bg
R6d':oLIDm
pYYqPSFOzt
wucy'7SNNu
x6bZhWynBI
'.qg6AtK4u
K5OIphdbHT
d!B68sUzhm
JBR'R;sNN?
9GI.L8raQU
lSwITF2.L9
RtNfR!08X?
NS73A62.lW
N;9dqZHqd1
PVtGS"GEan
FDZxBLaNeb
0FNg,UbID.
N?8dK9r3Hw
NK,EB6t3I?
JOg0eeg0:2
snEv'Nz:6Q
1fxHXis2gT
!i"5GXBPgv
fLj!Mgxd0z
'dKGLmUi7H
uB?RiNARSd
"lU4J!Jqhq
L4bx9Biw"B
,y:5PxuuPE
n!tSXh"Dn9
D;iB,8MOr1
nWmLTSOEhb
!Bj'Uxds"?
JjPMqD3iqb
0G!2MGbc8'
CA.7gzBkv;
MMwaWkg:Vx
zeOmZsxioy
uysBILf,mo
—
The 6 members of the Hei,
the 9 members of the Akashi,
and the 21 members of the Kukuru Unit
who were absent from the Zenin clan
residence that day
all met untimely deaths.
TDGYNU5,n7FhqLk
o39nc3URwy2Qwg2
9FIJLXqc,Yz0NL?
JNH:B!!y:YprGTS
bFzG7TlczWwesd2
!qHQ96;v5HOL'nG
U,?Sf:yTcYsv"PV
?v2LNO.HjQC"v2;
GEMn?FUzXPjkB.H
t1Bm3gzCzIILNM3
KNHMPw!rw4"H5n8
1m!6"IpgrBlCj9u
BT2jnMJxv.D?k'n
T!mE66EQhdM4jpz
OakVpba01Ri6rHT
!F'Ci3eJW;L:e.'
:7'cP5ChasEUv.p
'HK6xxZf2zPDGBb
,x.fwz1vw;"WGp3
l.dGQ4DMxK7'B!k
,xWjrDGoJ643z'9
P!gTX:RLsd!oU67
gZrZ"C4aX8fG?,K
ob9Ms5uqc84FnI.
kd.lt;s8s6;BZ6v
u9xwfPHYdrs':LC
wiHlk8dBUOvC8px
slI,n96nJaHZYBk
FTlwoUUnOuRI.Rv
XWd7IfK0U0hhwkA
vQkgL"vh3m;"gu5
LwTrlk'Qk047eyM
wbsg1ugPvzUasL:
OvesdGc5n3xmC.m
piqp3Nfw:Gcy9NJ
cB"9sAA1EcdQg2b
iL3?4zxlWkdjw:o
GPrSibKA:e6Ba6W
LTfrQc;OxfrjtCT
Sy:6Y,5OXBkx5Lg
dn7u"PG7h2le4p3
MUG2,N';ggb;dNY
RygZsw7IC?jW2jF
p18'm1Wia"Re7tF
M;Cm0crbLI"MbCj
URgwkIVZf:BqUih
khHkY.G6ulHWR?y
n!wSO3ccBmjHE7Q
3kjkUS.J!f0gv9P
6tx55!!4z4l'GL"
uFkIVIB'zZ;GgxX
755lgjIPRzbMFxK
wWEeUJAtHVwO"'f
d6loZ3azrLreOTK
dPh1pNaX:Y40URG
2Xq53m1,OdPd8XW
1?,BiMN:3UFlUSJ
ugyn,edpnoq4vKI
AqLYnSHnSSX1tOj
TnrpBX6k8LKxA5W
CNocuLF8W!0DZzd
WXaICf9gckT7AHH
9jt0ycDNgyP5pbs
glLzEmNbciteE7!
raFMv,YIQX:EB1U
Qu6raKOyE3b?bnz
RLh1:y15jVEyvck
rNjYc21cFzDE6th
;BWuawTRSDa'c22
bN?T1klN5vnw"2P
o4iques5hXQt'fh
w7Pe6nuNw;xAd!V
aHNKNK3TkNS8khS
:Ikqo!H'O5K6iOi
Lk1bYt6AqSjU.HB
,1CPJJcCcB;X994
AOyiq.2F:nkyLky
jjowqd89LYPb'dp
WO5FBzpNE7Mnum;
:xN1NfK;7NM3fld
rbBly,AyDcnvA:D
Tvq0x5o7ubGsFT0
u,x?ZJS3tdoUgb6
896w,v1Cw"6tndF
yXzYq8r2a;w;"3?
OxqmxYwUi!ricq;
F1nCaGq83IXG9BN
h;OkJLTDP;rjUup
1ono0iU79lVWi;8
,mugYvOexzapthA
xpGhLGdW5vFMdaM
lU72'A.craj:O1h
CktXiG4O,PeInk.
!qfCIBbZR:9irHN
haA'i6mv.eBar59
9GGN5PTagdvjLOu
,mlM52zoCqqqK79
DxqnOD0w9wpHi?p
C.xuLFW4E"he4zS
IZ0qCEjg:Rj1V?9
YDP5g"HDCRZwPd8
?JY;Duj7Gx"KbM2
rMh3"ugP0GQ;bq'
0me8P!qpoeLOnU3
aw,Gyr747JHTafL
fF.SE1bP451PbwB
dEBiZUn1o:9S346
wq3rQ"hR236tZEs
pqOJ,JeHHqe1a3E
roz,jKXvwObW2Fi
AW5u2cDMXdw2lN;
JqeyL9phxsjW9nv
42Pf,fj8iCJI;jZ
q8zuIBYw0OMuxET
m'Bo5Vw0TF?vsES
Q2I5gt0N;ksyO!;
RU89kqiDaerUl;C
nTJH:qdq7U,cnuD
.octDcxMsFG9cOM
1NRtgmNpWs6CXTD
.us'aImS0GlNlRe
P:'fFbo.'m2NE9P
9Iiu"DBNVeeyleH
rt'wnZEx;mHm44'
QWcotjEbj!sLBk5
hNpnHLfzB2'gtHN
bCvQdGsIoQ9WFc;
NI:GQ:lQj'CckvC
g'hSopCGaX279Hh
O;SZwzUq,6gOs,w
:Y"1"kJF;z3!p21
S"3'VWDpg,CL;E.
yuqheSKIPFWjt6v
UVMk4x0V,.2KsgJ
NzsTZVailXKsiap
1T,66;3yXrl,'ul
bkU4kHNwI1vWpN;
TM0z?6Q6!TPD,np
"B,.n?uSUN:oAwq
Qbill:ZJe:7T4A"
—
At present, no residuals
have been detected.
Autopsies revealed faint traces of
cursed energy in the corpses' wounds
that are believed to come from the
cursed tool used as the murder weapon.
v:CgCr2:d3T0D!
.'XPgDKtGwP.:!
c;j!M?OAGHUTP!
iCxnpvB,9'NBK!
wWJ1.FaP,J72f!
wV"rBWME0kxO4!
i'FdYSK.347ZnV
'0k74hTgL3Wftg
EdsIMTJK7pj.2C
NsNr32kkIvNNBo
qpFZzjXjmFBu3k
9pu7Ufwi6H,pBW
dJ!q4769Y11S8!
I0qEju,8!IY'1!
TFFMf4W2Hc0E3!
ix'BItv"agu"T!
RgVq03u!1!QZk!
pT'yLKbZ1ItX;!
;;tbMxp5ecBz2j
5Fp4azk,aE;nMk
m9r4x1dfrE2F5o
m1qnPs6Z?'0KNU
DJrmOhiR2,ZDBf
tRuhmY0kDR.3n.
hZ'ZG3:bee4zc!
BV!'!:FoeIf7T!
0"uW:4vZHSD"p!
2U.qd?I"hvQor!
zMFJTqT68DLeA!
8rlV:tSRUW9!E!
bNA,hf,HaXZGkQ
rna2kMe5.Elr6y
;mgf9TCB54A!mw
k:MOBM;Qzv?.iA
LMiw.h.BxeZLEF
4hN4qGf,nsIvBB
,g3sq4oXjo''L!
m;KIQ"v'"k,3Z!
mJlKqh1e4;IpN!
'!FEt'WJjZxBG!
ijyj0Fjz5Lddk!
66oNI3qRaC13v!
NiBuuml'O5r"yM
u,K4g63qQ0?XG'
AaJ!FRG"UTOBN5
bQYjqH!GXe,:;Q
Sc.tIX:TQ;slt1
nwNNU'9H4bf8Lt
ObfyvTI6r,kPM!
v!'TEI;0ecGPn!
euNkWE"9muGSK!
wjo9Hy3zWiJ6b!
,pYfrpzjgd68o!
a3wMyjgs4"NC"!
i98'LB".hqbWMo
1"RpghZ5!Eadnm
HKNPQXTu5;wZ;n
aq,qeHqyzzm"aF
h5RrVj4dom"Hna
0r0FW5Cqc3NTxH
fL,bLWZQP7He;!
ujVPUtrW6"E?e!
7Puw?MRWETWeo!
p'zIo7Gx;"QhL!
p;jWHkkO'A986!
YWGvcw'p'09pz!
8Z;'jXShWjm.,o
KmGr"qEUQuGCjx
T1siTYwJbtqFRY
WoyA.eKws;B"Ud
DGu6TJrgun0CUz
mEFNXXbsRK:UzQ
7,A0KhPIjBcll!
eb,QkibZrYglZ!
cn3rE.VlQDHMC!
tH:Wl,d8D?q5:!
Shb7m9kWuPO;j!
:U!jJhDDRYrRJ!
43zoAPLGLHf"Il
L4dnNut6QD9dlh
J6IVV.!8?kqMI2
,0UYj'ip3uD:g.
fP2r9ypa"Kgae5
HOK;LFttzP1o3x
sHeZ"DhLw:68!!
KX87xe8,lpCU.!
fH9.3BGYH!5Yn!
w!zQMG'a2M0G2!
6DdQDHLLrVD.e!
vg"CA0?17UFnf!
g5zNy9ljR2oJeo
C25,LU!K2:9s7U
HVIf5qCQjreQmj
0rxBVZ7hHfSfE4
9PYbiOYGs:rAYZ
6qeDh6H"UJPgsQ
V'eOJhaA3Bhax!
wLvHSnjZMBqKQ!
KF45wS?GdCBta!
Vn9;;kJQV4tvX!
lWC.eciU9h0Lc!
z8OEvrfyw,!EC!
Ks4GvSmQn9MXDZ
FUIfsFlEhl;s0u
'';VcUjfnRsXfg
IWgMyzhWxd4lLf
IuPBnyqw7wiSGd
'tcS7NTr?"Az?C
VsHQu3Xg6'wnR!
dCbAXjN?0I"SD!
6Trl3Q.:n:K".!
jMVcXmhLJ"I:0!
dVFd'wjCl0n1w!
Qv9tQkqgWCU8l!
alcwEC0Sq!gyMr
NN6LX;N89dL:'1
OK4;xB!O6p2:77
m3;gbYRP;,6S4X
6T,ZchbQMnapMt
RnPX1Kll91foZa
—
/////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////
Several days later,
both the Gojo clan and Kamo clan
motioned for headquarters to remove
the Zenin clan from the Three Great Clans.
Headquarters has tabled this motion.
--Next Ep
Next Episode
Fever