JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
Juzo Kumiya's Masterpiece,
The Cursed Tool "Dragon Bone"
Secret Art: Falling Blossom Emotion
Technique Release - Blazing Courage
Episode 51
Perfect Preparation
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Kukuru Unit Captain, Nobuaki Zenin
Are you listening?
"Hei"
Head of the Hei, Naoya Zenin
The six members of the Hei,
the nine members of the Akashi,
and the 21 members of the Kukuru Unit
who were absent from the Zenin Clan's
home that day all met untimely deaths.
At present, no residuals have
been detected,
and autopsies revealed faint traces of
cursed energy in the corpses' wounds
that are believed to come from the
cursed tool used as the murder weapon.
Several days later,
both the Gojo Clan and Kamo Clan
motioned for headquarters
to remove the Zenin Clan
from the big three families.
Headquarters has tabled this motion.
Next Episode
Passion