JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
Episode 49
One More Time
Flowing Red Scale - Stack
Supernova
The Culling Game <General Rules>
1) After awakening their cursed technique,
players must go to a colony of their choice within 19 days
and pledge their participation in the culling game.
2) Players breaching the first rule shall be stripped of their technique.
3) Non-players shall become players upon entering a colony,
and their entry shall be taken as pledging to participate in the culling game.
4) Players will receive points upon ending the life of another player.
5) Points shall be designated based on the value that the game master gives their life,
and fundamentally a sorcerer will be worth 5 points
while non-sorcerers will be worth 1 point.
6) By spending 100 points,
not counting the initial point value assigned to them, players may negotiate
with the game master to add an additional rule to the culling game.
7) The game master must approve any additional rules
requested under Rule 6 above, except when the Rule
would significantly hinder the continuation of the culling game.
8) Players who do not show a change in points
within 19 days of joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
The Culling Game
General Rules
Within 19 Days
Participate
Breach
Technique
Stripped
Entering a Colony
Participate
Ending
the Life
Sorcerer 5 Points
Non-Sorcerer 1 Point
The Culling Game <General Rules>
1) After awakening their cursed technique,
players must go to a colony of their choice within 19 days
and pledge their participation in the culling game.
2) Players breaching the first rule shall be stripped of their technique.
3) Non-players shall become players upon entering a colony,
and their entry shall be taken as pledging to participate in the culling game.
4) Players will receive points upon ending the life of another player.
5) Points shall be designated based on the value that the game master gives their life,
and fundamentally a sorcerer will be worth 5 points
while non-sorcerers will be worth 1 point.
6) By spending 100 points,
not counting the initial point value assigned to them, players may negotiate
with the game master to add an additional rule to the culling game.
7) The game master must approve any additional rules
requested under Rule 6 above, except when the Rule
would significantly hinder the continuation of the culling game.
8) Players who do not show a change in points
within 19 days of joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Next Episode
About the Culling Game