Yaga, what is that thing?
I know man-made cursed corpses can act
more autonomously than other forms of manipulation,
but they're always powered
by cursed energy from the sorcerer.
Yet that thing is sustaining
itself on its own cursed energy.
The higher-ups are preparing
to formally designate you as special grade
and place you in indefinite detention.
Because if you can intentionally create that thing,
you could easily have your own army.
Answer me, Yaga.
Do you truly not know how that thing was made?
Correct.
Masamichi.
Everyone's worried about you.
They say you seem down.
Is that right.
So I told them all this!
If you're feeling down,
we just have to cheer you up!
That so?
I'm a genius, aren't I?
Yes, you are.
Takeru, I'm sorry, but I won't be able
to come home for a while.
Please let the others know, too.
Another work trip?
Yeah. It'll be a long one.
Don't worry.
This forest is protected by Master Tengen.
Your mom will come see you again, too.
You'll be all right without me.
Masamichi.
It'll be lonely without you, Masamichi.
Are you sure, Kusakabe?
Don't go telling anyone I helped you.
You were captured to lure Yaga out.
And I owe him a favor.
Go on, get!
You're sure about this?
This thing is not your nephew.
It's just something
with your nephew's information.
You're trying to say people can't live in the present
if they stay hung up on the dead, right?
Still, my little sister
can no longer live without Takeru.
Masamichi, that lady is my mom, isn't she?
Yeah. Good job recognizing her.
I had a feeling it was her.
I'm a genius, aren't I?
Takeru!
I'm sorry, but...
I know.
The existence of fully autonomous cursed corpses
can't be made public.
So they can't live together.
I'm sorry.
Why're you apologizing?
Thanks a lot.
I mean it.
Thank you.
Where do you think you're going
without your cursed corpses, Principal Yaga?
To see my son.
Since you've been sentenced to death,
allow me to tell you the one way to save your life.
Disclose how you create those fully
autonomous man-made cursed corpses!
You all sure grew bold
the moment Satoru was gone.
Principal.
I'll handle the rest. You may leave.
Understood.
You use the body's information
to reproduce the soul's information.
Then you place that soul information
in the cursed corpse's core.
But that alone isn't enough.
You have to place three highly compatible souls
into a single cursed corpse,
and have them observe each other at all times.
Doing that allows the souls to stabilize
so self-awareness can take root.
Roughly three months after that,
it will begin supplying its own cursed energy.
Why?!
Why tell me now?!
Why wouldn't you reveal that sooner?!
Why didn't you try to live?!
It's a curse, Principal Gakuganji.
A curse from me to you.
Masamichi!
Why don't you fight?
Do you not hate me?
Pandas aren't bound by things like that.
Besides, there wasn't any bad blood
between you and Masamichi.
To me, you're just the knife
that fell upon him.
But remember this...
Even pandas cry.
Hakari Kinji is currently in an
abandoned parking garage in Tochigi,
running an underground fight club to make money.
A fight club?
They host fist fights between sorcerers.
Then the spectators are...
Generally non-sorcerers.
That blatantly violates the secrecy
mandated in Article 8 of the Jujutsu Regulations.
There may be curse users among the fighters, as well.
Do be careful.
Why are we changing?
Hakari was suspended for clashing
with the higher-ups.
He's also actively violating jujutsu regulations.
If he finds out we're with Jujutsu Tech, he might run.
It's like we're the cops and he's the robber.
Hm?
We're on Jujutsu Tech's side now?
We're in the gray,
but in Hakari's eyes, we're with them.
Is he even gonna help us in the first place?
I'm not sure.
Our seniors all say he's a worthless bum.
But even Okkotsu said Hakari's stronger.
We definitely want his strength.
Beat it, brats.
This ain't a place for you to hang out.
I'm gonna count to three,
and you'd better be on your way out.
Anything else, and my fist gets involved.
We need money.
Let us enter the fights.
The first rule of Fight Club is:
You do not talk about Fight Club.
Now answer me. Who told you?
Then, my fist gets involved.
Didn't get his name before I killed him.
About a month ago, there was that scumbag
who was all talk, remember?
Kondo went missing about a month ago.
I'll fill his slot for you.
Or would you rather I lay you out
in front of your boss?
Oh, yeah.
He'd be on his guard if we suddenly asked to see him.
Yes.
We're not even supposed to know his name!
No, there's no proof.
I better zip it.
Are you sure?
That's enough.
The boss has given you the go-ahead.
We'll pit you against today's seeded fighter.
However, he's the one fighting.
That's good for us.
Itadori is better suited to the fighting.
No go. I'll fight.
Boss said he ain't betting on you.
If you don't like it, the deal's off.
Fine. We'll take it.
Fushiguro, that was risky. You were pushing it.
Not really.
If curse users are involved,
there must be decent turnover.
More importantly...
Yeah, they're here.
If he was watching us through security cameras,
there's a high chance Hakari is in here.
Itadori, you snoop around
from the inside.
I'll try to sneak into that
parking garage in the meantime.
Or maybe not.
Why not?
I think they want to see what I'm up to.
If they catch me sneaking in, we'll lose their trust
and our chance to meet Hakari.
If that happens, we'll just have to use force.
Only as a last resort.
We're only here to ask Hakari
for his cooperation.
I'd like to avoid anything that
might affect relations.
To be honest, I don't think
I should be doing anything tonight.
But I don't want to waste what time we have
before Tsumiki's deadline.
Right now...
it's 5 PM on the 10th.
That leaves us with nine days, huh?
Getting here took longer than expected.
So while I will be trying to look for Hakari tonight,
if it looks risky, I'll pull out.
I hope that answers your "why not."
Got it.
There are two rules.
No running away. No cursed techniques.
How come?
I don't mind if they use cursed techniques.
Because most of the spectators
are non-sorcerers. They can't see them.
If they can't see it, it won't hype them up.
And the "no running" rule?
It means you fight
where the spectators can see you.
All about the spectators, huh?
Obviously.
This is a business.
What's the boss like?
Curious?
Well, yeah.
You'll know if you meet him.
Can I meet him?
There are two kinds of matches.
Legit beat-downs like in today's tournament,
and scripted bouts.
The boss writes the scripts.
He might call for you
if you manage to shine out there.
In other words,
I just gotta put on a good show.
That makes things simple.
That's your opponent.
I was blown away
the first time I saw him, too.
Yeah?
It's really all about drawing in the crowd.
Now, we're getting started again tonight!
It's time for the Legit Fight Club Tournament!
Commentary will be provided by
yours truly, John☆Bobby!
Allow me to introduce tonight's exciting match-up!
We're joined by a sudden upstart!
Will he rise up or burn out?!
It's the Dangerous Fireball Kid, Yuji Itadori!
He stands like a panda!
He sits like a panda! He walks like a panda!
Panda!
Now, hurry up and place your bets!
Everyone ready?!
Let's get ready to rumble!
I can feel the heat dying down.
What's wrong, Kin?
Luck is meant to be tested, y'know.
There's no thrill in betting on a sure win.
There aren't many stray sorcerers
who are tough enough to beat Panda.
Holy smokes!
This is the best bout in my career as a commentator!
Looks like you might be wrong.
Huh?
Did you manage to see Hakari?
Nope.
He's not on guard since we know each other,
but he's avoiding me.
The other third-year's technique is also a problem.
You’re undercover here, right?
Yeah.
Good, good.
You know what to do now, right?
Whoa!
This is definitely the best bout in my career as a commentator!
I've only been at this for a couple weeks, though!
The winner: Itadori!
What a punch!
I can't move!
The Animal Welfare Society won't stand for this!
Your acting sucks.
Send Itadori up to the roof when the tournament's over.
Huh?
He's sure to win 'em all.
Plus, he's intentionally taking the fight upward
to impress the crowd above.
I can write a good script with him.
And like I always say, strike while the iron's hot.
That's so dumb. Cut it out.
Got it. And what about the other brat?
Continue to stay sharp.
I'll send Kirara for extra security later.
Whaaat?
I'm feeling a nice buzz now.
I haven't felt this alive
since my ex maxed out my credit cards.
Quit bringing up your ex!
I see.
Sounds like Itadori might make contact
with Hakari after all.
Why haven't you been able to see him yet?
Well, I do know where he is,
in the monitor room on the roof,
but I just can't get close.
Why is that?
Even when I approach the door,
I can't close the distance.
The sensation is similar to
Satoru's technique.
I think it's because of Kirara's technique.
Kirara?
The other third-year was a guy, right?
Yep, a guy.
So does that phenomenon only occur
when Kirara is in the monitor room?
I don't know.
I focused on being a circus panda
instead of pushing too far and making them run off.
I'm glad you two showed up.
Do you think Itadori can convince him?
It'll be tough, but it might come down to timing.
Itadori's bright and charming personality
is a good match for Hakari.
But we all know he sucks at lying.
He doesn't just suck at it.
He struggles to even see it as an option.
So once Itadori enters the monitoring room,
I'll take control of the place quickly and quietly
to buy time for the two of them to talk.
Um, I don't think—
Don't worry. I'll just put them to sleep.
I know where the cameras are
and their blind spots.
How many guards?
Four at the entrance.
Two on each floor, except the roof.
We can handle that.
The only real concern is Kirara's technique.
We can't do much about that.
If they can warp Itadori out of there
or warp in some backup,
we'll have to give up
on getting through to Hakari.
You're still a first-year, Yu?
You're young!
"Yu"?
Kin had to repeat a year in middle school.
You sound happy.
Because I am.
It's been a while since Kin's been this hot.
You see, I love it when Kin is hot.
Itadori.
Would you believe me if I said you could work
one hour a day and make one million yen a month?
Uh...
Hm?
Depends on what the work is.
Well, for that information,
you'll have to pay 200,000 yen.
Really?
I don't believe you, then.
Good. Like you suspected,
that's a classic con.
The swindler pretends to be rich,
sells you a way to get rich, and takes your money.
It's obvious if you think about it,
but there's a stupid number of idiots who fall for it.
Why?
It's all because of fever.
Fever?
Both the swindler and the deceived are in
a fever to change their lives.
People get high on fever
and lose sight of their judgment.
Yet they can't even fall in love without it.
I love the fever.
Do you know the most direct way
of dealing with fever?
Gambling?
I knew you'd get it.
Life is a gamble.
Loads of women have dumped me
because they hate gambling,
but they've got it all wrong.
Our society tramples on those who can't bet big
and those who don't know when to fold.
There isn't a single person who doesn't gamble.
What people hate isn't the gambling,
it's losing and being ruined.
Don't some people
just want to live a peaceful life?
I dunno anyone like that.
I love the fever.
Fever is gambling. Gambling is life.
And love is control.
Someday, I want to control
this country's fever through my Fight Club.
With the existence of curses going public
and headquarters barely functioning,
I've got a chance to expand the business.
I'm going to crush the obstacles before me
and make them publicly recognize my Fight Club
in the coming revisions to the jujutsu regulations.
At any rate, I'll need a strong piece on the board.
Itadori.
Wanna get high on my fever?
Boss, I need to—
Itadori, want something to drink?
Oh, I'm good with anything.
Other than liquor.
What, can't handle it?
It's not that. I'm still underage.
You don't strike me as the type who cares.
Did you know
Gojo Satoru can't hold his liquor, either?
Really? Who's Gojo?
And I never said I couldn't.
Look.
Huh?
There isn't a single sorcerer
who hasn't heard of Gojo Satoru.
So why did you play dumb?
Were you...
sent by Jujutsu Tech?
Listen! I—
H-Hey!
L-Lis—
When I get a call from Kirara,
it means something's up.
Listen to me!
Hell no!
Now I've gone cold!
If we can convince them,
negotiations with Hakari will go more smoothly!
Wait, Kirara!
Stay out of this!
You have to show me! Right here and now!
Please! There's no time!
Kin's in danger!