Episode 48
Execution
JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game
The Culling Game Part 1
Special First-Grade Sorcerer    Naoya Zenin
Special First-Grade Sorcerer    Ogi Zenin
Special First-Grade Sorcerer    Jinichi Zenin
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Third-rate
When a sorcerer is inexperienced with manipulating cursed energy, there's a deviation in the
cursed energy during their preliminary movements, allowing the prediction of their next action.
When they have mastered manipulating cursed energy, there is no such deviation in their cursed energy, making it difficult to predict their action until the last second.
First-rate
Next Episode
One More Time