So, she's dead?
That one, Mai.
It's the clan head you
should be concerned about.
Besides, the one on the verge of death is Maki.
That so? Good thing, that.
Maki's a real beauty, but she's no good.
She doesn't know how to support a man.
Any woman who can't walk three steps behind a man
should be stabbed in the back and left to die.
Mai's a great woman in that regard.
She's got the same face and the same tits as Maki.
Though she acts tough,
she understands her place as a woman.
You're late.
What were you so occupied with
while your own father is at death's door?
Whoops.
But what's it matter if I'm here or not?
I'm gonna be the next head of the Zenin Clan anyway.
My older brothers are all useless bums.
And Uncle, you haven't amounted to much
despite being his little brother.
Your daughters are out of the question, too.
And Jinichi, well...
You're just ugly.
Woulda been better if you got Toji's looks.
Papa's at death's door, y'know?
Cut him some slack.
I see everyone's here.
The head of the Zenin Clan,
Lord Zenin Naobito, has just passed away.
I, Furudate, am in possession of his will.
I shall read this will in accordance with
Lord Naobito's final wishes.
Lord Zenin Ogi.
Lord Zenin Jinichi.
Lord Zenin Naoya.
I am to read the will once all three of you are gathered.
If there are no objections,
then I shall begin the reading of his will.
First, the 27th head of the Zenin Clan
shall be Zenin Naoya.
Second, all assets and cursed tools held within
the Cursed Warehouses of Jujutsu Tech and the Zenin Clan
shall be inherited by Naoya.
Naoya shall require approval from either
Zenin Ogi or Zenin Jinichi to make use of their contents.
Tch.
Well, that's fine.
However,
in the event that Gojo Satoru has died, or is otherwise mentally incapacitated,
then the covenant with Fushiguro Toji
shall see Fushiguro Megumi be brought into the Zenin Clan,
whereupon he shall become the head of the Zenin Clan,
and all assets shall pass to him.
What?
I won't stand for this.
Those two got no balls.
They ain't doing jack 'cause they'd rather have
some random brat over me as the head.
Where's Megumi right now and what's he doing?
I don't know the details,
only that he's in Tokyo,
assigned to search for Itadori Yuji.
Who's that?
The vessel of Sukuna.
Then go tell the big shots
that Zenin Naoya is gonna kill Sukuna's vessel.
Megumi is with Sukuna's vessel, yeah?
I'll kill 'em both at once.
Tokyo is pandemonium right now.
Anyone can die there at any time.
Once I kill him, the rest will work itself out.
I'm the head of the Zenin Clan!
I should've died.
Kugisaki!
It should've been me!
You've got it from here.
Just kill yourself!
Itadori.
What will you do?
Yuji.
How are your injuries?
Other than the ones
from Black Flash, they're healed.
It's probably because of Sukuna.
I can feel his power growing.
Yuji.
Don't worry about me.
You can return to Jujutsu Tech, you know.
I'd like to retrieve the remains of
Shoso and the others, too.
I'm not worried.
This isn't about whether I want to go back or not.
Sukuna is plotting something
that involves Fushiguro.
Besides, I've killed so many people.
What will you do when someone you saved today
kills someone else in the future?
I can't stay with the others anymore.
And are you okay with this, Choso?
I killed your brothers, too.
It's fine. That was an accident.
Eso and Kechizu would say the same in my position.
There was never a question about forgiveness.
That's what it means to be brothers.
Let's go.
We need to thin out the curses.
Choso!
Yuji.
How terrifying.
I already sensed he was powerful when we fought.
Now there's a subtlety to it as well.
Unfaltering control of cursed energy.
Exceptional physical strength.
Truly a demon!
He isn't even in top shape yet.
That's my little brother.
You're still saying that?
I'll say it as many times as it takes.
Try to recall.
They should have been there.
Your father should have had
stitches on his forehead, too.
Megumi ain't here.
I'm the first to arrive?
Really now? He's that slow?
Who's this guy?
Did he just mention Fushiguro?
What're y'all doing, anyway?
You stand out too much.
Not gonna run?
Why would I?
What, you don't know?
You're marked for execution,
now that Satoru's protection is gone.
His whims and influence have saved many a sorcerer!
My business is with Megumi, so to be blunt,
I couldn't care less if you live or die.
Don't want you running around willy-nilly, though,
so I'm gonna break your legs for now.
What do you want with Fushiguro?
I want him dead.
Though it'd be great for me
if he'd write a few lines before he goes.
I heard he's been searching for you.
He's fast, sure, but there's more to it.
It must be his technique.
You're doing better than I expected.
Not that I expected much.
I get the deal with the vessel,
but what's that thing beside him?
Guess I'll crank the speed up a bit.
Mr. Gojo?!
No, it's something more sinister!
Oh? He's not alone.
Who are you?
Whoever he is,
his target appears to be...
What are each of you to Itadori?
So he's here to carry out Yuji's execution.
Hold up. I'm on your side.
You're Okkotsu, yeah?
Okkotsu!
The second-year Fushiguro mentioned!
A special-grade sorcerer, like Mr. Gojo!
And you are?
I'm Zenin Naoya.
Maki's cousin.
I've been told to kill Itadori, like you were.
You need to run, Yuji.
So relax. I'll stay outta your way.
What?
The blond one's a speed type
with some kind of trick.
Playing chase with him is not a good idea.
I'll stall him.
Will you be okay?
In return, once you've killed Itadori,
could you hold off on reporting it for a bit?
He's bait for someone I wanna meet.
I'll be fine.
You're the one they're after, Yuji.
Focus on getting away
from that black-haired one, Okkotsu.
He's the same type as Gojo Satoru.
You'll die if you fight him.
Good thing he didn't hear me mention Megumi.
Gave me the chills.
This way, Yuji won't have to fight another human
or feel bad about leaving me.
He's such a handful.
We'll meet up at yesterday's spot!
Fine by me.
I'll leave that one to you, then.
All right!
He's fast!
All while holding a drawn sword?!
He's fast.
I expected to take him out in the initial rush.
Tch!
I was trying to block Okkotsu's path,
but he read my intentions!
I was watching earlier.
That's Blood Manipulation, yeah?
Dunno why you have it, though.
Still, aside from Piercing Blood,
it's nothing too scary.
And Piercing Blood takes Convergence.
That's a long build-up.
Need I say more?
It's checkmate. You're gonna die.
Worry about yourself.
Do you think you can walk away alive
after trying to hurt my little brother?
I was sure that would've cut him.
He's like Maki.
Surprised?
I don't look like the power type, do I?
It's not raw power,
he has an insane amount of cursed energy!
I'm actually on the weaker side.
He compensates for his lack of strength
with cursed energy reinforcement.
Everyone does that to some degree,
but the way he uses it is...
The exact opposite of me, then.
Have you noticed?
I have more cursed energy than Mr. Gojo, even.
But he has the Six Eyes,
so he wastes practically no energy
when activating his technique.
He's the best there is when it comes to efficiency.
I can run out of cursed energy, but not him.
And now, I'm done talking.
Shit!
The flow of cursed energy
of an elite sorcerer is difficult to read,
but for different reasons than yours.
That's because an elite sorcerer
can manipulate cursed energy more precisely.
Meaning you can't predict their attacks
until the last second.
But this guy...
His entire body, even his sword, is bursting with cursed energy!
Reading his movements is out of the question!
Any of his attacks can be fatal!
And he can minimize any damage he takes, too.
You've got it from here.
Sorry, but I can't afford to die just yet!
Some center their training around the use of a weapon,
but I don't want you relying on cursed tools
and neglecting cursed energy manipulation.
You're still a ways off on that front.
Slaughter Demon is for emergencies only.
I never got the chance to learn this!
You're too focused on the blade.
It broke?
Can't say I'm surprised.
He is one of Mr. Gojo's students.
I guess you won't go down easy.
The wound's deep but my guts are intact!
And now we're both unarmed!
I can win this!
What are you doing?
We're just playing, Rika.
Rika?!
What is this thing? A cursed beast?!
Where did it come from?!
Hold him still.
I can't move!
It's too strong!
I'm sorry,
Itadori.
Older brothers inferior to their younger brother
have no reason to exist.
I can't understand
how you could never love your brothers.
...could you please report Itadori's death...
...that might've been when
everything started to go wrong.
Don't look down on me!
So start by saving me...
It's checkmate.
Tsumiki has been ensnared in this game.