Nice to meet you.
Child of Zenin, Descendant of Michizane,
Cursed Womb Death Painting,
and Vessel of Sukuna.
No greeting for me, Tengen?
So this...
So this thing...
So this person...
Person?
...is Tengen?!
It's not our first time meeting,
Tsukumo Yuki.
Why did you close the Tombs of the Star?
I was wary of you being
aligned with Kenjaku.
I can't tell what's going on
in people's hearts, after all.
Kenjaku?
What was once Kamo Noritoshi.
The sorcerer currently inhabiting
Suguru Geto's body.
A net of compassion and
a rope of salvation, huh?
He didn't even try for
sarcasm with that name.
Why are you like that, Master Tengen?
Ballsy of him to insert himself
into the conversation there...
I'm immortal, but not ageless.
You'd look like this, too,
if you were 500 years old.
Seriously?
Since I failed to assimilate
with the Star Plasma Vessel twelve
years ago, my aging has accelerated,
and my identity as an
individual has vanished,
so the world itself is who I am now.
So there wasn't actually another
Star Plasma Vessel back then?
That explains why there isn't a new voice.
Excuse me.
We came here to learn Kenjaku's goal
and how to open the Prison Realm.
Could you tell us what you know?
Of course.
Or so I'd like to say, but I
must impose one condition.
Okkotsu Yuta.
Tsukumo Yuki.
Cursed Womb Death Painting.
I'll need two of you three to remain here
and guard me.
Guard you? But you're immortal, right?
Are you afraid of being sealed or something?
That isn't fair.
You won't tell us why or
how long we're guarding you?
In that case,
let me speak of Kenjaku.
That man's objective
is to force the evolution of
mankind throughout all of Japan.
I heard about that.
But how does he actually intend to do it?
Why didn't Kenjaku use your barriers
to turn everyone in Japan
into jujutsu sorcerers
with Idle Transfiguration back then?
Because he simply lacked the
cursed energy to do that.
The cursed energy refined through
Maelstrom can't return to the sorcerer.
Also, evolving people one person at a time
with a cursed technique is far too inefficient.
So the method of evolution
that Kenjaku has chosen
is to assimilate mankind with me.
Huh? But your assimilation...
...should only be possible with
the Star Plasma Vessel.
Previously, that was true.
But since I started evolving
twelve years ago,
assimilation with someone other than
the Star Plasma Vessel is possible.
But you're just one person, right?
How would you assimilate
with multiple people?
What you see before you right
now isn't my real self.
Now that I've evolved,
my soul is everywhere.
I told you, didn't I?
The world itself is who I am now.
People who assimilated with me now would
become something more than a sorcerer.
They would become a new being
that's both there and not there.
I'm able to retain my shape and reason
after evolving because of
my barrier techniques.
However, if mankind were to evolve,
then if even one of them
went out of control,
the world would end.
Why?
There would be no boundaries
between individuals,
so evil would spread to all instantly.
The impurities of a hundred million
people would flood the world.
What happened in Tokyo would be
recreated on a worldwide scale.
Why would he do such a thing?
I don't know.
I told you that, too.
I can't tell what's going
on in people's hearts.
But wouldn't everything be fine as long
as you rejected the assimilation?
That's the issue.
Now that I've evolved, my nature is closer to
that of a Cursed Spirit than a human.
So I can be
targeted by Cursed Spirit Manipulation.
Considering Kenjaku's
strength as a sorcerer,
I would likely be absorbed
the moment he made contact.
That's why my main body is rejecting
everything in the
Tombs of the Star right now.
That's why you want us to guard you?
Yes.
Kenjaku is second only to me in
his skill with barrier techniques.
I don't know when he'll manage to break
the seal on the Tombs of the Star.
Why now?
You were stopped from assimilating
with the Star Plasma Vessel.
Now you've been forced to evolve,
and he seeks to absorb you with
Cursed Energy Manipulation.
Kenjaku also seems to have
connections to Sukuna.
So he's been a sorcerer
for at least 1,000 years.
So why now?!
Because I, the Star Plasma
Vessel, and the Six Eyes
are all connected by fate.
Twice in the past, Kenjaku was stopped
by the sorcerer with the Six Eyes.
The second time, Kenjaku was thorough.
He killed both the Star
Plasma Vessel and the bearer
of the Six Eyes within
a month of their birth.
Despite that, the Six Eyes
and the Star Plasma Vessel
still appeared by the
day of my assimilation.
After that, Kenjaku altered his
strategy to focus on sealing
the Six Eyes instead of killing him,
and he began searching
for the Prison Realm,
because there can't be two people
with the Six Eyes at the same time.
However, twelve years ago,
something unpredictable happened.
Toji Zenin intervened.
He was physically gifted
through a Heavenly Binding Vow.
And he was unique among them
for being completely
free from cursed energy.
Since his Heavenly Binding Vow
placed him outside of fate,
he destroyed the fate connecting us.
Then a young man with power of
Cursed Spirit Manipulation appeared.
Without even trying,
he now had all the necessary pieces
other than the Prison Realm.
Then, six years ago,
the Prison Realm made its way
into Kenjaku's hands, as well.
Then why is this
Culling Game being hosted?
It's a warm-up before assimilation.
My assimilation with people other
than the Star Plasma Vessel is possible,
but at the moment,
there's a high probability
it will result in something incomplete.
The Culling Game uses the
cursed energy of the Players
and the boundaries formed
between the Colonies
in a ritual to send this nation's
people to the other side.
He probably plans to use that as a warm-up
to start their assimilation with me.
However, in order to establish that ritual,
Kenjaku should have been forced
to accept several pacts.
One of them is that Kenjaku cannot be the
Game Master of the Culling Game himself.
However, that still serves as
a disadvantage to you all,
because it means that killing Kenjaku
won't end the Culling Game.
Either all of the Players must die,
or the Players must all refuse
to participate and die.
The Culling Game won't end until then.
The "continuation" mentioned
in the Culling Game's rules
is insurance to prevent the
ritual from being stopped.
In that case...
Yeah.
We'll need to participate
in the Culling Game,
and add a rule that creates
a way out of the game
for Tsumiki and those
reluctant to participate.
We also need to free Mr. Gojo
at the same time.
That man could resolve
everything on his own.
Master Tengen.
First, please decide who will stay.
I will stay.
Yuji, you will absolutely need the
help of Okkotsu or that woman.
Kamo Noritoshi...
If Kenjaku is coming after Tengen,
that's all the more reason for me to stay.
Because slaying him will
save my younger brothers.
I'm still not finished
talking with Tengen.
Is that okay, Okkotsu?
Yes!
I don't want to be separated
from everyone anymore, either!
Thank you.
This...
is the "Back" of the Prison Realm
that you'll need in order
to free Gojo Satoru.
Back?!
First I've heard of it.
You mean like a back door?
That's right.
Before Kenjaku found it,
the Prison Realm was
outside of my barriers.
Probably somewhere abroad.
By keeping this Back sealed,
I concealed the presence of the Front,
but it didn't work.
Gojo Satoru is also sealed
away within this back gate.
Huh?! Then if we open it...
No, the authority to open the gates rests
with the owner of the Front—Kenjaku.
In order to break this one open,
you need either the Inverted
Spear of Heaven that can force
the cancellation of cursed techniques,
or the Black Rope that can
disrupt and cancel out the effects
of a cursed technique.
However, twelve years ago,
Gojo Satoru either sealed the Inverted
Spear of Heaven abroad or destroyed it.
Why'd you do that, Teach?!
The Black Rope was also completely
expended against Gojo Satoru last year.
What was that man thinking?!
Oh.
Miguel and I were searching
Africa for more of that Black Rope.
So that's why you were abroad.
It was a complete waste of effort, though.
They said it's all gone.
Huh?!
There's still some way, right?
Yes.
Among the Players participating
in the Culling Game,
there's a sorcerer from 1,000 years
ago who calls herself "Angel."
Her cursed technique can extinguish
any other cursed technique.
Extinguish any cursed technique?
Yes.
The Angel's cursed technique can
open the Back of the Prison Realm.
Do you know where she is right now?
She's in the Colony on
the east side of Tokyo.
The Culling Game's barriers reject me,
so I don't have more
information than that.
Let's start going over things from there.
There are ten Colonies across Japan.
They are linked by barriers designed to
ferry the people of
Japan to the other side.
Crossing a river or other border—
acts that symbolize crossing
to the afterlife—
carry important meaning in sorcery.
Oh, it's like with Yasohachi Bridge!
Is Hokkaido excluded because of
the Jujutsu Society's barrier?
That's right.
That land is already established
as a vast sacred ground.
That's "the challenging land" for you.
"Ferry them to the other side"
may sound dramatic,
but everyone in Japan was cursed in
preparation for the assimilation.
How long will this ritual take to complete?
That depends on the Culling Game,
but it'll probably be
over within two months.
It's currently 9 AM on November 9th.
The Players awakened as sorcerers
around midnight on October 31st.
We have about ten days and fifteen hours
before Tsumiki's forced to participate.
Master Tengen, you said earlier
that people would die if
they refused to participate.
Yes.
Stripped of their technique?
That rule also applies to sorcerers
joining in later, right?
Then the stripping isn't being
done by Idle Transfiguration.
It says "stripped," not "prohibited
from using," so it's not a Binding Vow, either.
That means it'll be doing something
to the brain by force,
and it's better for the rules if
being stripped means death, too.
Otherwise, everyone would
refuse to participate.
It's just as Shoko anticipated,
but that also means there's no risk
to sorcerers without any
cursed technique, like me.
And what'll happen to Panda?
Does he even have a brain?
What does this rule mean for the ordinary
people who were in the Colony from the start?
It means they're granted at
least one chance to leave.
For real?
That's awfully generous.
There are no stipulations in the rules
about leaving or entering Colonies.
They were probably aiming to stimulate the
Culling Game by giving Players a clear,
initial goal of leaving the Colony.
In order to keep the Players inside,
the premise that Players "entered of
their own free will" is important.
The thing about adjusting the barrier
strength that Ino mentioned?
Using "fundamentally" within a rule?
Way to make things confusing.
Fushiguro?
It's nothing.
Master Tengen, who is this Game Master?
Every individual Player is given
a shikigami called "Kogane."
To be precise, Kogane isn't the
Game Master—it's an interface.
It's best to think of the Culling Game
system itself as the Game Master.
I see...
"Add," huh?
So no eliminating any existing rules.
We might be able to refute
them in a roundabout way.
Is this allowed?
Right?
It leans too heavily on their judgment.
No, you should be able to
expect a fair decision here.
They're already imposing such
strong rules on the Players.
Jujutsu sorcery wouldn't allow them
to favor Kenjaku any further.
So I'll kill people again?
No, I have a few ideas.
We've managed to organize
our information for now.
That just leaves the roles for each of us.
Yuki and Choso will remain
here to guard Master Tengen.
I need to return to the Zenin house
and retrieve their cursed tools.
Shortly after Satoru was sealed,
the Kamo and Zenin Clans
both took their cursed tools
out of Jujutsu Tech's
forbidden vault, so it's empty.
However, Megumi's now the
head of the Zenin Clan.
Oh?!
I'll explain later.
Thanks to that, we're free to rummage
through the Zenin Clan's forbidden vault.
But before that, Master Tengen...
I know.
Juzo Kumiya's atelier, right?
Thank you.
Once I'm finished, I'll look for Panda
and help deal with the Culling Game.
And you, Yuta?
I'll enter a Colony and participate
in the Culling Game right away.
I'd like to gather as much
information as possible
before Tsumiki and Fushiguro
participate in the Culling Game.
Thank you.
It'll mean acting on my own again,
but to prevent us from
clashing with each other,
and to avoid running into her if
something does happen to Tsumiki,
I'll stay away from the nearby Colonies.
The Colonies might cut off reception,
so I might be out of
contact for a while...
If Sukuna does manage
to take control again,
don't hesitate to kill me.
Is this the time to worry about that?
It'll be fine.
If that happens, you can
have him kill you after I die.
No, I'm trying to prevent that.
Senpai.
Yeah.
You two go to see Kinji like we planned.
Kinji?
Hakari Kinji.
The suspended third-year.
We're shorthanded right now.
Do whatever it takes to recruit him.
Is he strong?
He's a bit capricious,
but when he gets into it,
he's stronger than me.
That's impossible.
Choso!
Thank you. You've been a big help.
Don't die out there.
Are you crying?
Shush.
Th-Thanks for tonight!
Takaba!
How long are ya gonna
keep doin' that crap?!
Cut it out!
You're making me depressed, too!
Yeah.
How old are ya now?
Thirty-five!
Then give it up already.
Our industry's full o' late-bloomers who
suddenly make it big for no good reason,
but none of 'em suddenly got funnier.
They were just funny people
waiting to be discovered.
And that ain't the case for you!
Look what happened to Tokyo.
No one's gonna think ill of you.
Go do something you're actually suited for.
I never disliked your comedy, Takaba.
Ken?
Both you and him have the wrong idea.
There's still people who ain't
funny that make it big.
You mean those with one stock gag?
Nah.
There are two types of comedians
that manage to stay big.
Comedians who are always funny,
and comedians who can always delude
themselves into believing they're funny.
Which one are you?
I'd say it's 50-50,
but it's actually 70-30...
50-50...
I'd say it's 50-50,
but it's actually 70-30!
Mai, I'll get started.
Why did you come here?
Shall I bully you like I used to?
Then, please, you do it, Maki.
You are me, and I am you.
Make me happy I gave birth to you.
Absolutely ridiculous.
Destroy it all.