Seriously?
Kenjaku's Objective
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
Idle Transfiguration
Insufficient Cursed Energy
Kenjaku's Objective
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
How?
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Why?
Unknown
How?
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Tengen
Star Plasma Vessel
Ordinary Person
Assimilation Possible
Assimilation Impossible
Star Plasma Vessel's Death
Assimilation With the Star Plasma Vessel Prevented
Tengen
Tengen's Evolution
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Out of Control
Kenjaku's Objective
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
How?
Why?
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Unknown
Kenjaku's Objective
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
How?
Why?
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Unknown
Why?
Geto Suguru's Death
Obtained Curse Manipulation
Obtained Idle Transfiguration
Star Plasma Vessel's Death
Tengen's Evolution
Obtain Tengen
Assimilation With Star Plasma Vessel Prevented
Tengen's Evolution
Obtain Tengen
Assimilation With Star Plasma Vessel Prevented
Tengen's Evolution
Obtain Tengen
Tengen
Star Plasma Vessel
Six Eyes
Kenjaku's Objective
Stop Tengen's Assimilation
Unpredicted Event
Zenin Toji Intervenes
Kenjaku's Objective
Star Plasma Vessel's Death
Curse Manipulation
Prison Realm
The Culling Game
Mankind
Tengen
Assimilation
Incomplete
The Culling Game
Mankind
Tengen
The Culling Game
Warm-Up
Assimilation
Success
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
The Culling Game
Mankind
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
Tengen
The Culling Game
Details
7. The Game Master must accept any proposed new rule in accordance with the previous rule unless it would have a marked and long-lasting effect on the Culling Game.
Player
Dead
Refuse to Participate
7. The Game Master must
long-lasting effect
6. Players may spend 100 points to negotiate with the Game Master to add one new rule to the Culling Game, excluding the initial point value assigned to their own lives.
spend 100 points
add one new rule
Itadori's Friends' Objective
Create a Rule to Escape the Culling Game
Free Gojo Satoru
Tell us
Prison Realm Back
Prison Realm
Gojo Satoru
Prison Realm Back
Inverted Spear of Heaven
Black Rope
They said there's none left.
Prison Realm Back
Inverted Spear of Heaven
Black Rope
Angel
Kurusu Hana
Episode 50
About the Culling Game
Gojo Satoru
Prison Realm
Prison Realm Back
Angel
Yasohachi Bridge's River
Other Side
Colonies' Barriers
*"The Rugged Lands"
A catchphrase issued in '99 by the Hokkaido Government.
The Culling Game
Warm-Up
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
Warm-Up Complete
The Culling Game
1. After awakening their cursed technique, players must declare participation in the Culling Game at a colony of their choice within 19 days.
Time Remaining Until Tsumiki
Must Enter the Culling Game
Obtain 100 points and add a rule
allowing people to escape.
2. Players who fail to comply with the first rule shall be stripped of their technique.
stripped of their technique.
3. Non-players who enter a colony become players at the moment of entry and shall be considered to have declared participation in the Culling Game.
entry
4. Players score points upon ending the life of another player.
ending the life
5. Points indicate the value of a player’s life and are determined by the Game Master. As a general rule, sorcerers are worth 5 points and non-sorcerers are worth 1 point.
As a general rule, sorcerers are worth 5 points and non-sorcerers are worth 1 point.
Game Master
Kogane
Not the Game Master
5. Points indicate the value of a player’s life and are determined by the Game Master. As a general rule, sorcerers are worth 5 points and non-sorcerers are worth 1 point.
6. Players may spend 100 points to negotiate with the Game Master to add one new rule to the Culling Game, excluding the initial point value assigned to their own lives.
100 points
add one new rule
6. Players may spend 100 points to negotiate with the Game Master to add one new rule to the Culling Game, excluding the initial point value assigned to their own lives.
7. The Game Master must accept any proposed new rule in accordance with the previous rule unless it would have a marked and long-lasting effect on the Culling Game.
8. Players who do not show any change in points within 19 days of joining or acquiring points shall be stripped of their technique.
8. Players who do not show a
change in points within 19 days of
joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
do not show
a change
stripped of their technique
8. Players who do not show a
change in points within 19 days of
joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
The Culling Game
Future Actions
Choso
Tsukumo Yuki
Guard Tengen
Zenin Maki
Retrieve Cursed Tools from the Zenin Clan
Kumiya Juzo's Workshop
Zenin Maki
Retrieve Cursed Tools From the Zenin Clan
Okkotsu
Participate in the Culling Game
Meet Up With Panda
They're thinking that having Okkotsu near
Itadori would keep Fushiguro safe, but it
would be a more efficient use of their
forces for Okkotsu to act alone.
Fushiguro Megumi
Itadori Yuji
Meet Up With Hakari Kinji
Hakari Kinji
Kenjaku's Objective (Road Map)
1 Year Ago
Geto Suguru's Death
Obtained Curse Manipulation
Absorbed Mahito
Obtained Idle Transfiguration
Turn Mankind Throughout All Japan
Into Sorcerers With Idle Transfiguration
Insufficient Cursed Energy
12 Years Ago
Zenin Toji Intervenes
Amanai Riko Murdered
6 Years Ago
Obtained Prison Realm
Assimilate
Star Plasma
Vessel
Tengen
October 31st
Satoru Gojo Sealed
Guard   Fate
Six Eyes
Assimilation Failed
Tengen's Evolution
Becomes a Target for
Curse Manipulation
Assimilation With People Aside from
the Star Plasma Vessel Becomes Possible
Goal: Warm-Up for Assimilation
Absorb Tengen With Curse Manipulation
The Culling Game
Force Modern Sorcerers and Sorcerers Awakened
or Incarnated Through Idle Transfiguration to Fight
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
The Evolution of Mankind Throughout All Japan
The Culling Game's Objective
Colony
Idle Transfiguration
Modern Sorcerers
Incarnated Sorcerers
Those Whose Cursed
Techniques Awakened
Fight
The Culling Game: Rules
Stock Up Cursed Energy
Rule Forcing Them to Fight
Use Stocked-Up
Cursed Energy
to Move the Barriers
Designed to Ferry
the People of Japan
to the Other Side
10 Colonies Throughout Japan
Forced to Cross to the Other Side (= Cursed)
Warm-Up
Assimilate Mankind With Tengen
Itadori's Friends' Mission
1. Free Gojo Satoru
Tengen Possesses
Open Prison Realm Back
Obtain Prison Realm
Kenjaku Possess
Can't Do Without
the Front Gate
To Force It Open...
Inverted Spear
of Heaven
Black Rope
Angel
Culling Game Player
Gojo Satoru Destroyed
Miguel and Okkotsu Failed to Find
Technique That Extinguishes
All Cursed Techniques
In the Colony on the East Side of Tokyo
2. Rescue Tsumiki and
Reluctant Players
Spend 100 Points (Per Rules 6 and 7) to Add a Rule
7. ~Add a Rule Allowing Escape from the Culling Game
Persuade Players With 100 Points
and No Intention of Adding a Rule
Each Person's Actions
Maki
Go Retrieve Kumiya Juzo's Cursed Tools
Fushiguro Has Become
the Head of the Zenin Clan
Go to the Zenin Clan's Cursed Warehouse
Meet Up With Panda
Okkotsu
Go On
Ahead Alone
Gather Information
Itadori    Fushiguro
Recruit Help
Recruit Hakari Kinji
Tsukumo      Choso
Guard Tengen
Participate in the Culling Game
Remain in the Tombs of the Star
Culling Game Player
Takaba Fumihiko
Next Episode
Perfect Preparation